https://poetshouse.org/legal-disclaimers-privacy-policy/

Contact Us
Search for:
Search
Poets House uses its best efforts to respect and protect the privacy of our online visitors and donors.
Information Collected
We do not collect personally identifiable information from you unless you provide it to us voluntarily and knowingly. If, for example, you sign onto our mailing or e-mail lists, or register for a workshop, the information we may collect will include:
your name;
mailing address;
telephone number; and
email address.
If you purchase a membership or make a donation, we collect only the information listed above, together with your giving history. Payment details such as your credit card information are preserved at Poets House in hard copy only, as required for payment processing and tracking and not shared with others.
Concerning and Handling Personal Information
While we may share postal addresses with carefully selected literary organizations, Poets House will not share, sell, rent, or trade any other information about our donors and members with any third parties, nor will members and donors be included in any list sharing except as may occur in a random sampling of mailing addresses only.
All your personal information is stored in databases located on password-protected servers which are behind firewalls. Donations made through our Web site are encrypted using the industry standard Secure Socket Layer (128-bit SSL encryption) security protocol when processing financial transactions, making it difficult for anyone to intercept the information you send us. Our staff is educated about the importance of safeguarding your information. However, such precautions do not guarantee that our web site is invulnerable to all security breaks. Poets House makes no warranty, guarantee or representation that the use of our web site is protected from viruses, security threats or other vulnerabilities and that your information will always be secure.
Donor anonymity will be respected if requested and where applicable. Upon request, we allow you full access to your information and we will maintain its accuracy according to your instructions.
Purpose of Use and Disclosure of Information
Poets House strives to keep donors and members informed about how donations are used and their importance for continuing our programs. We send several e-mails and mailings a year to accomplish this, and include a donation coupon to invite financial support. Most Poets House supporters want to receive all of our e-mails, mailings and newsletters; however, you may opt out of any and all mailings by contacting us with your request.
Visitor logs are used on this site for statistical purposes only, to help Poets House improve the functionality of our web site. Poets House may automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser, which may include your IP address, session time, click path analysis, and the pages you request. We will only use this type data in an aggregate form which does not identify you personally.
External Websites
Our Privacy Statement applies only to your use of the Poets House web site. Our site contains links to other sites, and we are not responsible for the privacy practices of these sites. Links to other sites do not imply an endorsement of the material or policies of those web sites. You should read the privacy policies of each site you visit to determine what information they may be collecting from you.
Comments or questions regarding the Poets House Privacy Policy should be directed to:
E-mail: info@poetshouse.org
Phone: 212-431-7920
Mail: Poets House, Donor Privacy, 10 River Terrace, New York, NY 10282.
Thank you for visiting our site.
Like this page? Share it. Share on Facebook Share on Twitter Share via Email
Events Calendar
« December 2020
»
M
T
W
T
F
S
S
30
Digital Chapbook Collection
Explore Chapbooks of the Mimeo Revolution—rare poetry collections from the 1960s to the 1980s now available in digital form!
READ THE CHAPBOOKS
Poets House on TwitterPoets House@poetshouse·20 NovOn November 16, Poets House was forced to cease operations. We believe it’s important that you better understand the situation we were in.
Read our full response: https://poetshouse.org/poets-house-responds/Reply on Twitter 1329902387033747460Retweet on Twitter 13299023870337474604Like on Twitter 132990238703374746012Poets House@poetshouse·16 NovIt is with a heavy heart we announce that as of today, Poets House is temporarily suspending operations.
We deeply thank our beloved community for the opportunity to serve them for the past 35 years.
https://poetshouse.org/press-release-poets-house-announces-temporary-suspension-of-operations/Reply on Twitter 1328396368914894849Retweet on Twitter 1328396368914894849114Like on Twitter 1328396368914894849602Poets House on Instagram
Donald S. Lopez Jr., Jennifer Kwon Dobbs, and Thom
Wind
.
Monotonous words, like a broken gramophone.
Words from the Poetry Path:
.
A Small Needful Fact
“Traveler, there is no path.
The path is made by
“Rice and Beans”
.
“They are better
together
“from the woodlands of new york
lenape nation
so
Follow on Instagram
This error message is only visible to WordPress admins
Error: API requests are being delayed for this account. New posts will not be retrieved.Log in as an administrator and view the Instagram Feed settings page for more details.
